Victory

Onuoha

PROJECT MANAGER, STAFFING & RESOURCES

613-608-9686

<u>Victoryonuoha.com</u>
<u>VictoryOnuoha@cmail.carleton.ca</u>
<u>LinkedIn</u>
GitHub

PROFILE

Project Manager with proven experience in coordinating project management activities especially gathering resources & staffing and a background in healthcare. Coached teams of 20+ people using strong communication & project management skills over the past 4 years. Additional experience in software development projects using interpersonal skills, JavaScript, and MySQL.

SKILLS

Interpersonal, Analytical, Coordination,

Communication, Teamwork,

Organizational, Time Management,

Detail-oriented, Leadership, Analytical,

Problem Solving

Microsoft Office, **SharePoint**, Project

Administration, Project Management,

Change Management, Consulting, Sales,

Scheduling, KPI Tracking, Reporting,

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Node JS,

GitHub, Jira, Asana, Figma, Slack, MS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Medical Affair Manager | APPLETREE MEDICAL GROUP 09/2022 – PRESENT, Ottawa

- Coordinated with cross-functional teams to manage multiple projects and resources leading to \$3M growth in annual revenue.
- Partnered with internal & external teams using analytical, **problem-solving** & written skills to implement new onboarding systems & **solutions**, resulting in onboarding of 4+ new clients a month.
- Consulted with internal teams using **communication** & **interpersonal** skills to schedule staff for new clients resulting in 85% retention rate.

Executive Administrative Assistant | APPLETREE MEDICAL GROUP 11/2020 – 09/2022, Ottawa

- **Supported** Project leads/Managers to **gather resources** to meet requirements of 3 to 5 client projects using **organizational** skills.
- Utilized **reporting** & tracking tools like MS Project, Asana & Excel to track **KPI's**, forecast hiring & execute data analysis for 3+ projects.
- Scheduled & organized training for over 50+ team members to communicate project updates.

Co-founder & Project Manager | RIJE STUDIOS 05/2021 – PRESENT, Ottawa

- **Facilitated** staff scheduling across digital projects using tools such as WIX, WordPress & JavaScript by **liaising** with development team to create **project roadmap** for products that services over 150+ clients.
- Increased website **performance** & traffic by 30%s by utilizing SEO strategies & **project management skills** for 3+ digital products.

EDUCATION

BSc in Neuroscience & Psychology | Carleton University 09/2013 – 11/2017, Ottawa, Canada

CERTIFICATIONS

- Diploma, Web Development | BrainStation
 05 2022 08/2022, Ottawa, Canada
- Professional Certificate | Google Project Management 02/2023, Ottawa, Canada